3. Navigate to Amazon
1. openBrowser("")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. Thread.sleep(1000)
13. navigateToUrl(SiteURL)
17. Thread.sleep(1000)
9. Amazon product
3. Search product
7. click(findTestObject("Page_Amazon/btn_Searchicon"))
11. click(findTestObject("Page_Amazon/span_Apple iPhone11"))
17. Get product name
21. comment("Name of Website :- Amazon")
25. comment("Name of the product for Amazon :- " + sGetValue)
29. println("Name of Website :- Amazon")
33. println("Name of the product for Amazon :- " + sGetValue)
39. Get price
43. comment("Price of the product for Amazon :- " + sGetPrice)
47. println("Price of the product for Amazon :- " + sGetPrice)
51. Price_amazon = sGetPrice
57. Get URL
61. comment("Link for the product for Amazon :- " + sGetLink)
65. println("Link for the product for Amazon :- " + sGetLink)
69. closeBrowser()
15. Navigate to ebay
1. openBrowser("")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. Thread.sleep(1000)
13. navigateToUrl(SiteURL)
17. Thread.sleep(1000)
21. ebay product
3. Search product
7. click(findTestObject("Page_eBay/btn_Search_ebay"))
11. click(findTestObject("Page_eBay/link_product"))
17. Get product name
21. comment("Name of Website :- ebay")
25. comment("Name of the product for ebay :- " + sGetValue)
29. println("Name of Website :- ebay")
33. println("Name of the product for ebay :- " + sGetValue)
39. Get price
43. comment("Price of the product for ebay :- " + sGetPrice)
47. println("Price of the product for ebay :- " + sGetPrice)
51. Price_ebay = sGetPrice
57. Get URL
61. comment("Link for the product for ebay :- " + sGetLink)
65. println("Link for the product for ebay :- " + sGetLink)
69. closeBrowser()
27. Compare Price
1. priceAmazon = Price_amazon.split("\$")
5. priceebay = Price_ebay.split("\$")
9. comment("Price of product at Amazon  :-" + priceAmazon[1])
13. println(priceAmazon[1])
17. comment("Price of product at ebay :-" + priceebay[1])
21. println(priceebay[1])
25. priceeAmazonNew = Float.parseFloat(priceAmazon[1])
29. priceebayNew = Float.parseFloat(priceebay[1])
33. if (priceeAmazonNew < priceebayNew)
2. markPassed("ebay has lesser price value for product than Amazon")
6. markPassed("1. ebay price value for product :- " + Price_ebay)
10. markPassed("2. Amazon price value for product :- " + Price_amazon)
14. println("ebay has lesser price value for product than Amazon")
18. println("1. ebay price value for product :- " + Price_ebay)
22. println("2. Amazon price value for product :- " + Price_amazon)